Clubs serve an important part of our school's mission to create well-rounded citizens
学校生活の中で、クラブ活動は重要です
Extracurricular clubs are held after school and all students must join
クラブ活動は、放課後に行われ、学生は最低１つのクラブ活動に参加する必要があります
an extracurricular Club or team each term
スポーツクラブまたは、スポーツチーム
There's a wide variety of offerings run by Bodwell teachers
ボドウェルの教師によって、色々な種類のクラブ活動を提供しています
Clubs usually meet once occasionally twice each week during the term
それぞれのクラブは通常、週に約2回活動をしています
Students joining a sports team have more commitment during a competitive season
スポーツチームに参加している学生は、試合のシーズンには
involving frequent practices and playing matches with other schools
練習も多くなり、他の学校との試合で忙しくなります
Clubs and sports teams are an opportunity for students
クラブやスポーツチームは、学生と教師が
together with teachers to get to know one another through common interests.
同じ目標に向かって活動できる、いい機会となります
They are often away at students can develop a hobby,
また、学生は趣味を広げたり、新しいスキルを身に付けることができます
improve their interpersonal skills, and widen their life experience.
コミュニケーションスキルも向上しますし、見分も広がります
We have several music clubs such as the concert band and rock band.
コンサートバンドやロックバンドなど、音楽関係のクラブもあります
We have art clubs for students that need to build an art portfolio.
美術系に進む為の学生には、アートクラブがあります
Some clubs are more connected to academic areas like the Model United Nations,
学生国連のような、学術的なクラブもあります
public speaking, chess, or the robotics team.
スピーキング、チェス、またはロボット関係のクラブ
Physical fitness is a possibility for sports that are out of season focusing on skill development.
オフシーズンのスポーツ選手の為、体力アップに重点をおいたクラブ
Students work on physical fitness at local gyms or with equipment available at the school
地元のスポーツジムや学校のジムなどで、体力づくりに取り組んでいます
Every semester the club offerings vary from hiking outdoors to calligraphy indoors
毎学期、アウトドアからから室内での書道まで、幅広いクラブ活動を提供しています
Sports teams run for both boys and girls including
スポーツチームは、男子と女子の両方を対象としています
basketbal,l volleybal,l badminton, and swimming
バスケットボール、バレーボール、バドミントン、水泳など
Club experiences can be beneficial to supplemental applications to universities
また、クラブ活動での経験は、大学進学の際にも役立つことがあります
and we encourage students to make the most of everything the club system has to offer.
学生が、クラブ活動を多いに活用し、留学生活を有意義なものにする事を奨励しています